stilltasty.com 2017-11-21

# StillTasty.com | Privacy Policy

## STILLTASTY PRIVACY POLICY

We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of the users of our site. 

This privacy policy will advise you about how we use and protect your personal information, and about what choices you have concerning our use of such information. Please read this policy carefully. We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our site. We will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this policy regularly.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please send an email to: privacy@stilltasty.com.  

**Scope of Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy applies to your use of all the sites and services owned by StillTasty LLC referred to here as StillTasty and collectively "we," "us," or "our", including stilltasty.com and any other site that we own and operate or may own or operate in the future (collectively, the "Sites"). Unless we say otherwise, any references to the Sites in this privacy policy include all such sites. This privacy policy does not apply to your use of unaffiliated sites to which any of the Sites only link. This policy covers only information collected on the Sites and does not cover any information collected offline by us.

**Personal Identification Information**

We may request personal identification information from you (such as your name, street address, telephone number, credit card number, e-mail address, and/or any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of you) in connection with your use of, or participation in, membership registration for our contests, sweepstakes, promotions, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, content submissions, chats, bulletin boards, discussion groups, requests for suggestions, visitors' requests for free products or services or additional information (including via email to us), and in connection with other activities, services or resources we make available on any of our Sites. In all of these cases, we will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. Except as otherwise specified in this policy, we will never intentionally disclose any personal identification information about you as an individual user to any third party without having received your permission.

If you do provide us with personal information for any of these activities, we may use it to conduct the activity. We may also use cookie technology and Web beacons (discussed in detail below) to improve your experience of these activities, including to remember your preferences, customize the content and advertisements that you see or authenticate your access to your personal information. In addition, in the event your personally identifiable information is requested as part of our surveys, polls or promotions, such personally identifiable information may be added to your registration information.

We may also contact you to confirm your registration and about your account status, and regarding changes to the Sites' Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.

If you give us your permission, we may also use personal identification information for internal or external marketing and promotional purposes. On occasion, for example, we may send you e-mails to introduce a product or service that we think might be of interest to the users of our Sites. For us to obtain your permission to send you this information, we will give you an opportunity to "opt-in" at the time our request for your personal information is made. If you do "opt-in," you may choose to "opt-out" at any time, even after you have provided personal information, by following the procedures set forth below at the end of this Privacy Policy. Please note, however, that under certain circumstances, if you initially do not choose to "opt-in," or if you later "opt-out," you may not be eligible for certain benefits for which a name, e-mail address, telephone number or other personal identification information is needed.

We have the following exceptions to these policies: We will release specific information about you or your account to comply with any valid legal inquiry or process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute or court order. We will also release specific information in special cases, such as if there is an attempted breach of the security of the Sites, or a physical or property threat to you or others. We may also transfer user information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of related assets or corporate division or other fundamental corporate change.

In addition, on occasion, we may collect personal identification information from you in connection with optional contests, special offers or promotions. We will share such information with necessary third parties for the purpose of carrying out the contest, special offer or promotion. Your participation in the contest, special offer or promotion constitutes your consent to such disclosure and use of such information.

Further, the information you enter when making a purchase or an online donation will be shared with payment processors, financial gateways, and your credit card company to authorize credit card payments. Such information may also be shared with necessary third parties solely for the purpose or carrying out the transactions.

Please note that if you give out personal information online-for example, on one of our public or private forums such as a message board or chat room, folder, or chat IM feature-that information can be collected and used by third parties. Although we strive to protect our users' privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of information you post in these forums. You disclose such information at your own risk.

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your information and password. You shall be responsible for all uses of your registration, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your registration or password.

**Non-Personal Identification Information**

We collect non-personal identification information through the use of:

"Cookie" technology: A "cookie" is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system.

"IP address tracking": An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are on the Internet. When you request pages from our Sites, our servers log your IP address.

"Web beacons": A Web beacon, or "clear gif", is a small graphic image on a webpage or web-based document that a web site can use to determine information about a user.

Non-personal identification information might include the browser you use, the type of computer, technical information about your means of connection to our Sites - such as the operating systems and the Internet service providers utilized, and other similar information. Our systems may also automatically gather information about the areas you visit and search terms you utilize on our sites and about the links you may select from within our Sites to other areas of the World Wide Web or elsewhere online.

We use such information to administer the Sites, better manage advertising on the Sites, and, in the aggregate, to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Sites. This way we know which areas of our Sites are favorites of our users, which areas need improvement, and what technologies are being used so that we may continually improve our site.

We may share this aggregate statistical information with our partners, suppliers and other third parties, but we will not share any individual names, personal navigational or other personal information. For example, we may use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our Sites. We may share demographic and preference information with this company to allow them to display appropriate advertisements for you.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Sites and other sites on which we advertise. Third-party advertising technology uses information about your visits to the Sites and other sites on which we advertise. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed or recognized on your browser. In addition, we may use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits the Sites, and to learn which banner ads bring users to the Sites. 

Further, we currently contract with a third party web analytics provider to help manage and optimize our Sites. We use this service to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our Sites. To do this, we use Web beacons and cookie technology on the Sites. The type of information we collect includes the number of hits a web page receives, type of browser used, and number of times a visitor makes a purchase from a particular promotion. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products and services most interest our users, and what kinds of offers our users like to see. Although this third-party provider logs the information coming from our Sites on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used.

**Privacy of Children**

We understand that young people need special safeguards and privacy protection. We realize that they may not understand all the provisions of our policy or be able to make thoughtful decisions about the choices that are made available to our adult users. We strongly urge all parents to participate in their children's exploration of the Internet and any online services, and to teach their children about protecting their personal information while online.

The Sites are not directed to children under the age of 13. We prohibit registration by children under the age of 13 for all interactive portions of the Sites including chats and message boards. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13.

We may, at our discretion, require users under the age of 18 to obtain the consent of a parent or guardian to view certain content, and we may limit access to certain content to users above a specified age. You agree to abide by any such restrictions, and not to help anyone avoid these restrictions.

**Links to Other Sites**

Users will find advertising or other content on our Sites that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the contents or links that appear on these site. In addition, these sites or services, including their contents and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies, or no policy (policies) at all. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information.

**Security Policy**

Protecting your privacy and your information is a top priority. We have taken careful measures to secure both your information and our physical premises. We exercise great care in providing safe transmission of your information from your PC to our servers (unless sent by a means outside of our control, such as e-mail). Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its security.

**Access To/Correction of Information**

If you would like to review any personal information we have retained about you in our database, please send us an e-mail request for this information at [privacy@stilltasty.com](mailto:privacy@stilltasty.com). To help us address your request, please specify which information you wish to review. Once you have reviewed this information, at your request we will correct personal information about you that you state is erroneous. To request such a correction, please send an e-mail to [privacy@stilltasty.com](mailto:privacy@stilltasty.com). You should be aware, however, that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our databases and servers although we will always make reasonable efforts to do so upon your request.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

If you "opt-in" to receive information from us or others, you can change your mind later. If at any time you would like to stop receiving such information or opt-out of a feature, you may go back to any of our sites and change your options. You should be aware, however, that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our databases and servers although we will always make reasonable efforts to do so upon your request.

**Consent to Transfer**

The Sites are operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our Web Sites, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using any of the Sites, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Sites. Your continued use of the Sites following the posting of changes shall constitute your acceptance of those changes.

(Last modified on December 2, 2009.)
